Guide to the Stanford University Video Collection SC1031
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Videos
  - SITN guest lecture series, 1986; V120; 1 videotape(s) (u-matic)
    Haley, Alex; Chisholm, Shirley; Tutu, Desmond
  - Jennifer Azzi highlights; Kodak All-American candidate, V121; 1 videotape(s) (u-matic)
    Women's basketball; Athletics; Azzi, Jennifer
  - Moses Pendleton presents Moses Pendleton, 1986 May 31; V122; 1 videotape(s) (u-matic)
    Pendleton, Moses
  - Pope on a rope (in San Francisco), 9/17/1987; V123; 1 videotape(s) (u-matic)
  - Happy McCluskey Day, 10/17/1979; V124; 1 videotape(s) (u-matic)
  - Card vs. Utes (athletic event?), V125; 1 videotape(s) (u-matic)
    Athletics
  - Western culture lecture by Ron Bracewell, 5/28/1981; V126; 1 videotape(s) (u-matic)
    Bracewell, Ronald; Western culture
  - Ansel Adams, 1982-1983; V127; 11 videotape(s); 11 videotapes (.75 inch)
    Adams, Ansel
  - Jesse Jackson, January 15 [?]; V128; 6 videotape(s); 6 videotapes (.75 inch)
    Jackson, Jesse
  - Donald Kennedy interview, 3/29/1984; V129; 4 videotape(s) (3 U-Matic, 1 VHS); 4 videotapes (.75 inch)
    Kennedy, Donald.
  - President Kennedy and Sally Ride, 4/26/1984; V130; 1 videotape(s) (u-matic)
    Kennedy, Donald.; Ride, Sally
  - Kennedy/Carter visit, 1983; V131; 1 videotape(s) (u-matic)
    High technology; Carter, Jimmy; Kennedy, Donald.; distinguished visitors
  - First David Starr Jordan Award; Donald Kennedy, Stanford University, V132; 1 videotape(s) (u-matic)
  - Labor of Angels: the restoration of Stanford University's Memorial Church, 1993; V133; 1 videotape(s) (vhs)
    Memorial Church; Loma Prieta earthquake
  - Barney's dance piece, 8/12/1986; V134; 1 videotape(s) (u-matic)
    Dance.
  - Dance concert master, V135; 1 videotape(s) (u-matic)
  - Jean Siegman - ACIS or ACTS, 10/21/1983; V136; 2 videotapes (.75 inch)
    Siegman, Jean
  - Gates Computer Science Bldg. Dedication--The Future of Computer Science Technology, 1996; V142; 1 videotape(s) (vhs)
    Freidenrich, John; Gates, Bill; Reddy, Raj; Computer science.
  - Stanford vs. Arizona (Men's Basketball), 1/15/1994; V143; 2 videotapes (.75 inch)
    basketball
  - Stanford vs. Arizona State (men's basketball), 2/10/1994; V144; 2 videotapes (.75 inch)
  - Stanford vs. Virginia (men's basketball), 12/22/1991; V145; 3 videotape(s); 3 videotapes (.75 inch)
  - Stanford vs. WSU (men's basketball), 1/8/1994; V146; 2 videotape(s); 2 videotapes (.75 inch)
  - Stanford at Oregon State (men's basketball), 2/5/1994; V147; 3 videotapes (.75 inch)
  - Stanford vs. UCLA (men's basketball), 1/27/1994; V148; 2 videotapes (.75 inch)
  - College Basketball: Stanford at Seton Hall Tournament, 12/30/1993; V149; 2 videotapes (.75 inch)
  - Stanford Basketball 1990-1991: Banquet Footage, 4/3/1991; V150; 1 videotape(s) (u-matic)
  - Stanford at Washington (women's basketball), 1/6/1994; V151; 2 videotapes (.75 inch)
    Women's basketball
  - NCAA-Dubs of Kodak All-American Videos with Jennifer Azzi and Trisha Stevens, 3/21/1990; V152; 1 videotape(s) (u-matic)
    Azzi, Jennifer; Women's basketball; Stevens, Trisha
  - Stanford Baseball, Stanford vs. USC, 4/9/1991; V153; 1 videotape(s) (u-matic)
    Baseball
  - Stanford vs. Ohio State (men's volleyball), 12/25/1994; V154; 1 videotape(s) (u-matic)
    volleyball
  - Stanford vs. Cal (men's water polo), 7/24/1991; V155; 2 videotapes (.75 inch)
  - Stanford Track and Field, 3/28/1992; V156; 3 videotapes (.75 inch)
  - Men's Tennis: Cal at Stanford, 2/29/1992; V157; 4 videotapes (.75 inch)
  - Men's Tennis: USC at Stanford, 4/4/1992; V158; 4 videotapes (.75 inch)
  - Slavic movies and TV programs (Video taped), 1986-1989; V163; 180 videotape(s) (vhs)
    Slavic studies
  - Protein synthesis [Paul Berg], 1971; V164; 1 videotape(s) (vhs)
    Biology.; Berg, Paul; Dance.
  - History and Hysterics: What About the Future?, 1996 Oct; V165; 1 videotape(s) (vhs)
    Conley, Frances; women and medicine
  - Silicon Valley: a 100 year renaissance, 1997; V166; 1 videotape(s) (vhs)
    Morgan, James; McLaughlin, John R.; Berg, Paul; Djerassi, Carl; Ellison, Larry; Computers.; Rodgers, T. J.; McNealy, Scott; Clark, Jim; Garcia, Jerry; Pauling, linus; Kennedy, Donald.; Silicon Valley; Electronics; Gibbons, Jim; Malone, Mike; Jobs, Steve, 1955-2011; Packard, David, 1912-1996
  - DNA Replication by Arthur Kornberg; [Scientific Symposium Tape #1: Genes and Chromosomes], 1980 Mar 27-28; V167; 1 videotape(s) (u-matic)
    DNA; genes; Kornberg, Arthur
  - Current Planning...Planning Futures, by David Neuman, 1997 Apr 29; V168; 1 videotape(s) (vhs)
    Planning; Neuman, David; Architecture.
  - Paul Berg discusses the Beckman Center, 1991 Sep 12; V169; 2 videotape(s)
    Berg, Paul; Beckman Center for Molecular and Genetic Medicine
  - Interview with Arthur Kornberg [Alpha Omega Alpha: leaders in American medicine], 1994 Dec; V170; 7 videotape(s)
    Lehman, Robert; Kornberg, Arthur
  - Living Legends: a discussion about the establishment of the comp. sci. dept. at S.U., 1997; V171; 1 videotape(s) (vhs)
    Computers.; computer science department; Knuth, Donald Ervin, 1938-; McCarthy, John, 1927-2011; Floyd, Robert W.; Miller, William F.; Herriot, John G., 1916-2003; Wiederhold, Gio, 1936-; Feigenbaum, Edward A.; Golub, Gene H. (Gene Howard), 1932-2007
  - Morrie Doyle: An Uncommon Man, 1997 Nov 13; V172; 7 videotape(s)
    Gardner, John; Doyle, Morris; Kennedy, Donald.; Brown, Douglas M.; Lyman, Richard W.
  - City of Palo Alto.--Sand Hill Road development, 1996-1997; V173; 32 videotape(s) (vhs)
    Palo Alto (Calif.); Sand Hill Road
  - Donald Knuth: Computer Science 209 lectures, 1987; V174; 31 videotape(s) (vhs)
    Knuth, Donald Ervin, 1938-
  - Choice and Vouchers: The Future of Education? (Series), 1993 Apr 30-May 1; V175; 15 videotape(s) (mii)
  - Hoover Drug Policy Program, 9/17/1991; V176; 3 videotape(s) (mii)
  - Eastern European Teleconference at Hoover Institution, 5/10/1991; V177; 2 videotape(s) (mii)
  - A Conversation with Herbert Hoover, 1960; V178; 1 videotape(s) (mii)
  - Hoover Conference: A. Polly Williams, 5/8/1992; V179; 1 videotape(s) (mii)
  - Hoover Institution: Prime Minister of Bulgaria, 3/8/1992; V180; 1 videotape(s) (mii)
  - George P. Schultz: Turmoil and Triumph, My Years as Secretary of State: Exhibit, V181; 1 videotape(s) (u-matic)
  - Hoover Institution Conference: Congressional Accountability, 1994 Feb 14-16; V182; 20 videotape(s) (mii)
  - Hoover Congress Reform Bumpers, 9/30/1994; V183; 1 videotape(s) (mii)
  - Congressional Reform Finance Bumps, 10/5/1994; V184; 1 videotape(s) (mii)
  - The Human Genome Project: Second Centennial Symposium, January 1991, 1991 Jan 11-13; V185; 20 videotape(s) (mii)
  - The Centennial Symposia: Third Event: Race, Ethnicity, 1991 Apr 11-14; V186; 9 videotape(s) (mii)
  - Program Symposia [possibly "Law School Conference: Women of Color"], 1990 Oct 6-7; V187; 20 videotape(s) (mii)
  - Legal Issues in Cyberspace, 1997; V188; 10 videotape(s) (vhs)
    internet; Business
  - Stanford Authors, 1995-1998; V189; 30 videotape(s) (vhs)
    Faculty
  - Women and Health, V190; 21 videotape(s) (vhs)
    Women.; Health
  - Charles Ferguson Remembrances, 1998 Sep 18; V191; 1 videotape(s) (vhs)
    Ferguson, Charles; Dept. of Linguistics
  - Nobel Perspectives on Ethics in Science, 1996; V192; 6 videotape(s) (vhs)
    Ethics; Science
  - Select Issues in Biomedical Ethics, 1998; V193; 10 videotape(s) (vhs)
    Medicine.; Ethics
  - Cantor Arts Center, 1999 Jan 13; V194; 2 videotape(s) (vhs)
    Museums.; Olcott, Richard; Faberman, Hilarie; Seligman, Thomas K.; Architecture.
  - Stanford campus views, early 1990s; V195; 1 videotape(s) (betacam)
    campus
  - "Good Morning America" being taped at Stanford with the focus on students and statement from Jack Hubbard, 1993 Nov 9; V196; 1 videotape(s) (vhs)
    Students; Shultz, George; Hubbard, Jack
  - Russia at the End of the 20th Century., 1998 Nov 6; V197; 8 videotape(s) (vhs)
    Post-communism; Russia
  - Human vs. Computer Creativity, 1997-1998; V198; 15 videotape(s) (vhs) (2 boxes)
  - Henry Fuchs Mechanical Engineering 245, 3/31/1982; V199; 1 videotape(s) (u-matic)
    Engineering.
  - Jasper Ridge Biological Preserve: An Island of Discovery, 1998; V200; 2 videotape(s) (vhs)
    Research; Jasper Ridge Biological Preserve (Calif.)
  - Highlights of a Team Season: Stanford Women's Basketball 1992 NCAA Champions, V201; 1 videotape(s) (vhs)
    Hemmer, Rachel; Kaplan, Anita; Whiting, Wal; Goodenbour, Molly; VanDerveer, Tara; Women.; Athletics; Students
  - The Big Game; A Century of Tradition, 1997; V202; 2 videotape(s) (vhs)
    Athletics; Big Game.
  - Inside Stanford Sports, V203; 3 videotape(s) (vhs)
    Oliver, Doug; VanDerveer, Tara; Kaplan, Anita; Brennan, Frank; Paye, Kate; Jerich, Mike; Shea, Terry; Athletics; Schlukebir, Katie
  - Scientific American Frontiers: Will Robots Take Over?, 1994; V204; 1 videotape(s) (vhs)
    Bear, John; Alda, Alan; flakey the robot; robots; Meyers, Karen
  - Multicultural Springfest, 2000 May 25; V205; 1 videotape(s) (vhs)
    staff; Hennessy, John L.
  - Becoming Stanford: the making of an American University, 1999; V206; 2 videotape(s) (vhs)
    Stanford University -- History.
  - Building for the Future: The Center for Cancer Treatment and Prevention/Ambulatory Care Pavilion, 1997; V207; 1 videotape(s) (vhs)
    Camran Nezhat; John Freidenrich; Gina Short; Sam Bronfman II; Jennifer Wolff; Charlotte Jacobs; Medical Center; Michael Dilingham; Sarah Donaldson; Branimir Sikic; Peter Egbert; Erik Skarsgard
  - Partners and Pioneers: The Center for Cancer Treatment and Prevention - S.U. Med Center, 1997; V208; 1 videotape(s) (vhs)
    Ellen Price; James Brooks; Saul Rosenberg; Branimir Sikic; Sam Bronfman II; Steanie Jeffrey; Charlotte Jacobs; Sarah Donaldson; Medical Center; Angela Johns; Gina Short; Robert Negrin
  - Bay Area Computer History Perspectives: Shakey the Robot, Oct. 25, 1995; V209; 2 videotape(s) (vhs)
    Donald, Bruce; Hart, Peter.; robots; Rosen, Charles; Russell, Stuart; Nilsson, Nils J.; Fikes, Richard; Artificial intelligence.; Raphael, Bertram
  - Celebration of a Presidency 1992-2000, V210; 1 videotape(s) (vhs)
    Casper, Gerhard.
  - Linda Meier: An Uncommon Woman, 2001; V211; 8 videotape(s)
    Uncommon Man Award; Meier, Linda
  - William Hewlett memorial service, 2001 Jan 20; V212; 1 videotape(s) (vhs)
    Hewlett, William R.
  - AI conference at SRI, 1999; V214; 12 videotape(s)
    Hobbs, Jerry R.; Artificial intelligence.; Hart, Peter.; Garvey, Thomas D.; Fischler, Martin A.; Bowles, Robert C.; Waldinger, Richard J.; Rosen, Charles.; Nilsson, Nils J.; Lowrance, John D.
  - Inauguration of John Hennessy as the Tenth President of Stanford University, 20-Oct-2000; V215; 3 videotape(s) (vhs)
    Stein, Isaac.; Casper, Gerhard.; Boland, Eavan.; Aquilanti, Giancarlo.; Presidents; Hennessy, John L.; Kennedy, Donald.; Lyman, Richard W.; McLennan, Scotty.
  - Yahoo! Jerry and Dave's Excellent Venture, 1997; V216; 1 videotape(s) (vhs)
    internet; Business; Alumni; Filo, David; Yang, Jerry
  - Connections; Stanford University Office of Technology Licensing, 1997; V217; 1 videotape(s) (vhs)
    Mejia, Luis R.; Scanning probe microscopy.; Ku, Katherine; Krensky, Alan M.; Patents.; Cohen, Stanley N.; Smith, Julius Orion.; Sandelin, Jon C.; Quate, Calvin F.; Watanabe, Mary K.; Wan, Mona M.; Murray, Walter.; Recombinant DNA; Synthesizer (Musical instrument); Reimers, Niels J.; Chowning, John M.; Clayberger, Carol A.
  - Channel 11 coverage of B160 time capsule, 16-Jul-2001; V218; 1 videotape(s) (vhs)
    Building 160; time capsules
  - Stanford Alumni Stories, Oct. 14, 1999; V219; 1 videotape(s) (vhs)
    Alumni
  - IFUW Conference, 1992; V220; 1 videotape(s) (vhs)
  - Stanford scenes [transferred from 8mm film], 1948-1951; V221; 1 videotape(s) (vhs)
    Football.; Stanford Village; Greek Olmpics; campus; Students
    - Duplicating master, 1 videotape(s) (minidv)
    - Use Copy
  - Norman Shumway tapes, 1990-1996; V222; videotapes
    Heart -- Surgery.; Shumway, Norman; Medical care.
  - William S. Johnson Symposium in Organic Chemistry (3rd: 1988: Stanford University), V223; 8 videotape(s) (vhs)
    Bartlett, Paul A.; Nakanishi, Koji; Danishetsky, Samuel; Williams, Dudley H.; Cram, Donald J.; Johnson, W. S.; organic chemistry; Knowles, Jeremy R.; Sharpless, K. Barry
  - William S. Johnson Symposium in Organic Chemistry (4th: 1989: Stanford University), V224; 7 videotape(s) (vhs)
  - William S. Johnson Symposium in Organic Chemistry (6th: 1991: Stanford University), V225; 14 videotape(s) (vhs)
  - William S. Johnson Symposium in Organic Chemistry (8th: 1993: Stanford University), V226; 4 videotape(s) (vhs)
  - William S. Johnson Symposium in Organic Chemistry (9th: 1994: Stanford University), V227; 6 videotape(s) (vhs)
  - William S. Johnson Symposium in Organic Chemistry (10th: 1995: Stanford University), V228; 10 videotape(s) (vhs)
  - William S. Johnson Symposium in Organic Chemistry (11th: 1996: Stanford University), V229; 7 videotape(s) (vhs)
  - William S. Johnson Symposium in Organic Chemistry (13th: 1998: Stanford University), V230; 7 videotape(s) (vhs)
  - Stanford School of Earth Sciences; a report to the alumni, 1990-1991, V231; 1 videotape(s) (vhs)
    Miller, Elizabeth L.; Hochella, Michael F.; Ernst, W. G.; Thompson, George A.; Earth Sciences.; Stebbins, Jonathan F.; Page, Benjamin M.; Orr, Franklin M., Jr.
  - Stanford Channel Master Tapes, V232
  - Dreams of a City: Creating East Palo Alto, 1997; V233; 1 videotape(s) (vhs)
    East Palo Alto (Calif.)
  - [Program on F. E. Terman], V234; 1 videotape(s) (vhs)
    Villard, Oswald G.; Terman, Frederick Emmons, 1900-1982; Lowood, Henry; Terman, Terrence C.
  - Stanford New SEQ, 1995; V235; 1 videotape(s) (betacam)
  - Discover Stanford, V236; 1 videotape(s) (vhs)
  - In the Stream of Time: A Portrait of Gordon Craig, V237; 1 videotape(s) (vhs)
    Craig, Gordon
  - Stanford Associates Awards Ceremony, 21-Apr-2001; V238; 1 videotape(s) (vhs)
    Stanford Associates
  - Stanford Associates Award Ceremony, 6-Apr-2002; V239; 1 videotape(s) (vhs)
  - Dallas Uncommon Man Ceremony, V240; 3 videotape(s) (vhs)
    Stanford Associates; Uncommon Man Award
  - The 27th Annual Viennese Ball, 2004; V241; 1 videotape(s) (vhs)
    Students; Dancing
  - Fathers and Sons, 1969; V242; 2 videotape(s) (betacam)
    anti-war protest; SDS; Pitzer, Kenneth; Franklin, Bruce
  - Cyberspace., 2002; V243; 3 videotape(s) (betacam)
    cyberspace security; Mueller, Robert; Clarke, Richard; Granick, Jennifer; Bennett, Ced
  - The Worlds Within [i.e. Stanford the World Within], V244; 1 videotape(s) (betacam)
    Electronics; Physics.
  - Human Biology class tapes, 1987-1989, 2001; V246; 51 videotape(s)
    Herant Katchadourian; Donald Kennedy; Jeffrey Wine; H. Craig Heller; Sandra Archibald; Sanford Dornbusch; Human biology; James Lawry
  - Health Care Education Network, V247; videotapes (Beta)
  - The Railroad Empire; buildng the iron horse, the transcontinental railroad and its impact on California, 2003; V248; 1 videotape(s) (vhs)
    Railroads
  - Stanford; the first 100 years, 1992; V249; 1 videotape(s) (vhs)
  - Issues and Ideas, V252; 11 videotape(s) (vhs)
    free speech; Homosexuality.; sexuality; race
  - Marta Sutton Weeks Distinguished Visitor lectures, V254; 11 videotape(s)
    film studies; gender; Williams, Linda; Fausto-Sterling, Anne
  - Life of the Mind, 1996-1998; V255; 8 videotape(s) (vhs)
    public role of the humanities; Reading; Ferris, William R.; Bloom, Harold
  - The Arts at Stanford, 2000; V256; 10 videotape(s) (vhs)
    Yvor Winters poetry; Irish poetry
  - Stanford Presents, V258; 4 videotape(s) (vhs)
    limits of performance; Music and the Holocaust
  - Globalization Conference--Global Mobility: Media and Minority Culture, 2003 Oct; V260; 5 videotape(s)
    Social software; Global media; Herz, JC
  - The Rebuilding Project: Iris & B. Gerald Cantor Center for Visual Arts, 1999 Jan; V261; 1 videotape(s) (vhs)
    Cantor Center
  - Levinthal Distinguished Speaker, 1992; V262; 6 videotape(s)
    Cage, John; Brodsky, Joseph
  - Of Mixed Minds, 1993; V263; 1 videotape(s) (vhs)
    Stanford Humanities Center
  - The 105th Opening Convocation of Stanford University: Casper Welcomes the Class of 1999, 1995; V270; 1 videotape(s) (vhs)
  - The 106th Opening Convocation of Stanford University, 1996; V271; 1 videotape(s) (vhs)
  - The 107th Opening Convocation of Stanford University, 1997; V272; 1 videotape(s) (vhs)
    Casper, Gerhard.; Senior B. Harris
  - The 108th Opening Convocation of Stanford University, 1998; V273; 1 videotape(s) (vhs)
    Casper, Gerhard.; Melora Krebs-Carter
  - Gerhard Casper. State of the University Address, 1993 Apr 29; V274; 1 videotape(s) (vhs)
  - Gerhard Casper. State of the University Address, 1996 Nov 6; V275; 1 videotape(s) (vhs)
  - Gerhard Casper. State of the University Address, 1997; V276; 1 videotape(s) (vhs)
  - Gerhard Casper. State of the University Address, 1998 Oct 29; V277; 1 videotape(s) (vhs)
  - Gerhard Casper. State of the University, 1999 Mar 2; V278; 1 videotape(s) (vhs)
  - Gerhard Casper: A Celebration of the First Five Years, 1997; V279; 1 videotape(s) (vhs)
  - The Celebration of a Presidency: The Gerhard Casper Years, 1992-2000, V280; 1 videotape(s) (vhs)
  - Gerhard Casper: press conferences and coverage, 1992-1999; V281; 5 videotape(s) (vhs)
  - Interchange. Interview with Gerhard Casper, 1996; V282; 1 videotape(s) (vhs)
  - In the Words of Gerhard Casper, V283; 1 videotape(s) (vhs)
  - Gerhard Casper. Lecture at George Mason University, 1994 Apr 19; V284; 1 videotape(s) (vhs)
  - The Future of Undergraduate Education, Gerhard Casper, 1993 Dec 16; V285; 1 videotape(s) (vhs)
    Casper, Gerhard.; undergraduate education
  - Come the Milleneum, Where the University? Gerhard Casper, Address to the A.E.R.A., 1995 Apr 18; V286; 1 videotape(s) (vhs)
  - Stanford architecture tour, Gerhard Casper, circa 1990; V287; 1 videotape(s) (vhs)
  - Purdue University. Gerhard Casper addresses Judiciary Conference, 1989 Sep 21; V288; 1 videotape(s) (vhs)
  - 50 Jahre Bundesverfassungsgericht, Festakt im Badischen Staatstheather in Karlsruhe., 2001 Sep 28; V289; 4 videotape(s) (vhs)
  - Forum on Higher Education, Peking U. Centennial. Gerhard Casper, 1998; V290; 1 videotape(s) (vhs)
  - Gerhard Casper at the Palo Alto City Council, 1993 Feb 16; V291; 1 videotape(s) (vhs)
    Palo Alto (Calif.); Casper, Gerhard.
  - Gerhard Casper at Bloomingdale's Opening, 1996 Nov; V292; 1 videotape(s) (vhs)
  - Breyer confirmation hearing. Testimony by Gerhard Casper, Kathleen Sullivan., 1994 Jul 15; V293; 1 videotape(s) (vhs)
    Biden, Joseph; Breyer, Stephen G.; Sullivan, Kathleen; Casper, Gerhard.
  - Does the Consitution Still Work? Perspectives on the Framers' Vision., 1997 Nov; V294; 1 videotape(s) (vhs)
    Polsby, Nelson W.; Sullivan, Kathleen; Casper, Gerhard.; Rakove, Jack N.; Constitution
  - Stanford Campaign for Undergraduate Education, 2001; V295; 2 videotape(s) (vhs)
    Hennessy, John L.; Casper, Gerhard.; Yang, Jerry; Yamazaki, Akiko
  - Clintons' arrival and departure at the Quad, 1997 Sep 19; V296; 1 videotape(s) (vhs)
    Clinton, Chelsea; Clinton, Hilary; Clinton, Bill
  - "Steel Seizure" Retrial - 50th Anniversary Celebration of Kirkwood Moot Court Competition, 2002 Oct 19; V297; 1 videotape(s) (vhs)
    Casper, Gerhard.; O'Connor, Sandra Day; Sullivan, Kathleen; Rehnquist, William
  - Bing Wing Re-opening Ceremonies, 1999 Oct 12; V298; 1 videotape(s) (vhs)
    Robert Bass; Judith Goldstein; Casper, Gerhard.; John Bender; Keller, Michael
  - Hoover Institution Board of Overseers Dinner featuring Lady Margaret Thatcher, 2000 Jul 19; V299; 1 videotape(s) (vhs)
    Thatcher, Margaret; Casper, Gerhard.
  - Go West. Film by Werner Siebeck [in German] which includes interview with Gerhard Casper on campus., circa 1990; V300; 1 videotape(s) (vhs)
  - Apostrophes a Stanford: Deux philosophes Francais en Californie, 1989; V301; 1 videotape(s) (vhs)
    Harrison, Robert Pogue; McGinnis, Reginald; Dickason, Margaret; Winslow, Bruce; Serres, Michel; Pivot, Bernard; Saint Amand, Pierre; Girard, Rene
  - Visit of Emperor and Empress of Japan to Hoover House, 1994 Jun 23; V302; 2 videotape(s) (vhs)
  - Achtung, Weenie. Big Game Gaieties, 1992; V303; 1 videotape(s) (vhs)
    Casper, Gerhard.; Gaieties; Ram's Head
  - Farm Wars: The Berkeley Menace. Big Game Gaieties, 1999; V304; 1 videotape(s) (vhs)
    Gaieties; Ram's Head; Casper, Gerhard.
  - Pres. Vaclav Havel's Visit to Stanford. Selected shots, 1994 Sep; V305; 1 videotape(s) (vhs)
    Havel, Vaclav; Brest, John; Baez, Joan
  - Pacific Vision; the Asia/Pacific Scholars Program at Stanford University, 1999; V306; 1 videotape(s) (vhs)
    Casper, Gerhard.; Asia/Pacific Scholars Program
  - Paris and New York in the Early 20th Century. Stanford Continuing Studies Class taught by Wanda Corn, 1997; V307; 10 videotape(s) (vhs)
    Corn, Wanda
  - Class of 1960. Reunion panel discusssion, Oct 13, 1995; V308; 16 videotape(s)
  - Stanford vs. Nebraska (1941 Rose Bowl footage) and home videos, circa 1941; V309; 1 videotape(s) (vhs)
    A 48-minute compilation of home videos includes footage from a vacation to Florida, the 52nd Annual Tournament of Roses, the 1941 Rose Bowl where Stanford beat Nebraska 21-13, a trip to California’s Death Valley, and an unidentified cattle ranch. The video has no audio.
    Stanford University -- Athletics; Rose Bowl
  - Fairchild Semiconductor 50th anniversary, 2007; V311; 2 videotape(s)
    Julius Blank; Jay Last; Gordon Moore; Arthur Rock; Computer industry.
  - Spirit of Stanford, 1942; V312
    Albert, Frankie, 1920-2002
  - Stanford Presents: Globalization: Brave New world or Plus ca Change?, 1999; V313; 2 videotape(s) (vhs)
    Holloway, David; Krasner, Stephen; Bardy, David; McKinnon, Ronald
  - Films shot at Stanford and elsewhere, 1939-1942; V314; 2 optical disc(s) (dvd)
    Student life.
  - The Challenging Era, 1962; V315; 1 optical disc(s) (dvd)
    Guerard, Albert J. (Albert Joseph), 1914-; Bush, Chilton; Rathbun, Harry; Sterling, J. E. Wallace; Fund raising.; Craig, Gordon
  - PACE announcement luncheon, 1961 Apr; V316; 1 optical disc(s) (dvd)
    Fund raising.; Sterling, J. E. Wallace
  - Campaign for Stanford, 1975; V317; 1 optical disc(s) (dvd)
    Lyman, Richard W.; Construction; Kennedy, Donald.; classrooms; Student life.
  - Edge of Greatness, circa 1962; V318; 1 optical disc(s) (dvd)
    overseas campuses; Students; Sterling, J. E. Wallace; classes; Sports
  - International Relations Program. Honors papers presentations, 1998-2002; V319; 39 videotape(s) (vhs)
  - Legagy of Shockley Semiconductor [roundtable discussion], 2005 Sep 27; V320; 1 videotape(s) (dvcam)
  - Whole Earth symposium, 2006 Nov 9; V321; 3 videotape(s)
    Rheingold, Howard; Turner, Fred; Brand, Stewart; Kelly, Kevin
  - SLAC's 40th anniversary celebration, 2002 Oct 2; V322; 2 videotape(s) (vhs)
    Panofsky, W.; Hennessy, John L.; SLAC; Dorfan, Jonathan
  - Stanford University. Libraries. Social Sciences Resource Center. Symposiums, 2003-2005; V323; 45 videotape(s)
  - The Spirit of Saroyan: video of program presented by The Arts at Stanford, 1997 Oct; V324; 2 videotape(s) (vhs)
    Saroyan, William
  - Stress portrait of a killer, 2008; V325; 1 optical disc(s) (dvd)
    Sapolsky, Robert
  - Shakey: Experiments in Robot Planning and Learning, 1972; V326; 1 optical disc(s) (dvd)
    Artificial intelligence.; robots
  - Bwana Nugu "Mister Baboon": adventures in neuroscience with Robert Sapolsky, 2004; V327; 1 optical disc(s) (dvd)
    Sapolsky, Robert; Neuroscience; Baboons.
  - Ninth annual Galarza Lecture, Dr. Jorge Bustamante, speaker, 1994 Apr 29; V328; 1 videotape(s)
    Galarza Memorial Lectures; Bustamante, Jorge